Finding Aid for Christ Episcopal Church (Owosso, Mich.) records, 1858-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Christ Episcopal Church (Owosso, Mich.) records 1858-1968
Christ Episcopal Church (Owosso, Mich.) records
1 linear foot
86937 Ba 2
Church minutes, financial reports and budgets, and miscellaneous correspondence and newspaper clippings.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records came from the church (donor nos. 5215 and 5785 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
Christ Church, Owosso, was founded in 1858. The cornerstone for the first church building was laid in September 1859. It was not until 1871 that the building was consecrated. In 1892, the church was remodeled and enlarged.
The records of the church go back to its founding in 1858. Included are minutes, parish registers, a scrapbook of events, and miscellaneous correspondence, reports and financial materials.
Subjects:
Episcopal Church--Michigan--Owosso.; Owosso (Mich.)
- Minutes, 1858-1966
  - 1858-1892 (Box 1)
  - 1892-1928 (Box 1)
  - 1928-1942 (Box 1)
  - 1942-1948 (Box 1)
  - 1955-1962 (Box 1)
  - 1963-1966 (Box 1)
- Parish register, 1858-1906
  - 1858-1891 (Box 1)
    (microfilm copy available)
  - 1892-1906 (Box 1)
- Other Records
  - Miscellaneous reports and minutes, 1960-1968 (Box 1)
  - Financial reports and budgets, 1958-1968 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1965 (Box 1)
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1917-1928 (Box 1)